宝贝 过来看看这个
Baby, check this out.
灰尘清除机
A power washer?
我们需要一台
We need one of these.
哦
Yeah.
- 在后院的天台  - 哦
- On the patio in the backyard. - Yeah.
我们该去看看窗帘吗
Should we go look at those window treatments?
不
No.
吃根热狗怎么样
Do you want one of these hotdogs?
很好吃的
They're vey good.
宝贝 你真是个好家庭主夫
Baby, you are a heck of a homemaker.
你知道吗
You know that?
其实我们可以到外面吃
But we could just go to dinner.
嗯 你知道
Well, you know...
如果你不做饭
if you don't make it...
你不吃的话
You don't eat it.
这主意还是不错的
You know what? That's a great idea.
我给你做晚餐怎么样
What if I make you dinner?
我去选一些新鲜的烤肉
I'm gonna go and get that grill. The big shiny one.
你去选几只大虾 好吗
Will you get us some shrimp? The big jumbo kind.
直走 在第三区
4 down. 3 over.
回来时我会都选好在购物篮里
Come back and find me down here. In tools.
你在这里干什么
What the hell are you doing here?
你没回我的信息
You ignored my messages.
我很快乐
I am happy.
你很绝望
You're desperate.
我能完成这项任务
I can make this work.
法兰克 你在玩家家酒
You're playing house.
听着 我退休了 我很高兴 我们很幸福
Look, I'm retired. I'm happy. We are happy.
法兰克
Frank...
已经好几个月没有杀人了
You haven't killed anybody in months.
这不是件坏事 对吗
That is not a bad thing.
对很多人来说
That's a positive thing for a lot of people.
我需要你 他们就要来了 我有预感
Kemosabe, I need you. They're coming. I can feel it.
这是要把我逼疯了 马文
You are driving me nuts, Marvin.
把那女孩一起带来 可能你会好受点
If it makes you feel better, bring the girl.
我才不会带上她
I'm not gonna bring the girl anmhere.
不带女孩去哪里
Don't bring the girl where?
因为恰巧  什么
We're just catching up.
碰到马文 我跟他聊了一下
Marvin's here. I just bumped into Marvin.
我们要去哪里
Where are we going?
不早了他们要打烊了
No, come on. They're gonna close.
很高兴见到你 马文
Good to see you, Marvin.
很高兴见到你
Good to see you.
法兰克
Frank.
你知道你想的
You know you want to.
不
No.
来吧
Come on.
最后的机会 法兰克
Last chance, Frank.
我带莎拉回家去
I'm taking Sarah home.
小心
Stay safe.
我真的想
Well, I really wanted to be...
当然 宝贝
Of course, it is, honey.
你再也不会身陷险地了 不会了
You are never gonna be in danger ever again.
我们甚至不知道发生什么事了
We don't even know what happened.
我们都不知道谁在那里
We don't know who's in there.
我到底该如何保护你
How am I gonna protect you?
嘿 他是你最好的朋友
Hey. He was your best friend.
不是吗
Come on.
哇
Wow.
他还是那么栩栩如生
He still looks so lifelike.
好像仍然活着
He's not dead.
不要这样 把感伤发泄出来
Don't do that. Just let your feelings out.
不 真的
No. Really.
他经常这么做
He does this a lot.
对吗
Really?
不要这样 把针给我
No, come on. Give me the pin.
来吧 亲爱的 快坐下
Come on, sweetie. Let's go sit down.
我应该先亲他的
I should kiss him.
你要就去吧
Go ahead. Do you want to?
让我们坐下 来吧 亲爱的
Let's go sit down. Come on, sweetie.
这一刻 我们将开放
At this time, we'll open the floor to anyone...
希望有人对死者说几句话
who wishes to say a few words about the deceased.
宝贝
Babe...
分享回忆
Share a memoy, perhaps?
或者咏诗 或歌曲
Perhaps, a poem. A song lyric.
谁来
Anyone?
你可以的
You can do it.
先生
Sir?
马文
Marvin was...
与众不同
different.
他
He was...
一个好人
a vey good shot.
有人说
Some would say that...
他很偏执
he was paranoid.
但是你也能想到些
But you have to expect a little of that...
因为中情局给了LSD
when the CIA's dosing you with LSD...
差不多十年了
for a little more than a decade.
他可以引爆一个炸弹
He could wire a bomb...
比任何人都要快
faster than anybody I ever met.
我所知道的人当中
The good people of Moldova will always...
马文是最好的
be in Marvin's debt.
他是个真正的好朋友
He was a really good friend.
真的很好
Really good.
我会怀念他的
I'm gonna miss him.
会想念他的
Gonna miss him.
我们该走了
We have to move.
加拿大
Canada?
离开这危险之地 那里有个小农场
High ground. Good kill zones. It's a little farm.
农场 像耕农一样
A farm? Like, to farm on?
像种小麦
Like, with crops?
是啊 很有趣
Yeah. It could be fun.
听着 宝贝
Listen, babe...
你要知道人们常说 重要的是经过
You know they say it's really important not to make big...
危难之后才会做出选择
life altering decisions right after a loss.
他们可以杀了马文 也可以杀了你或我
If they can get to Marvin, they can get to you and they can get to me.
他们是谁
Who are they?
到安全的地方去
Go to the safe house.
看着我
Look at me.
到安全的地方去
Go to the safe house.
我会去找你的
I'll come find you.
我不会离开你的
I'm not leaving you.
真的没事的
It'll be All right.
这是什么
What is it?
摩西先生
Mr. Moses...
他们要你做一份白扬基的汇报
They want to debrief you at a Yankee White facility.
是你的狙击手吗
Is that your sniper?
你是认为是"危险退休人员"
You're flagged Retired E_remely Dangerous.
白扬基
YANKEE WHITE FACILITY
你好
Hi there.
我的客户法兰克・摩西是在这里
My client Frank Moses is here.
他是美国公民 未经正当程序被非法拘留
He's an American citizen being detained illegally without due process.
可爱的夹克
That is a lovely blazer.
谢谢
Thank you. That is a lovely blazer.
不客气
Thank you.
抱歉 我不知道 让我帮你打给斯奈德先生
You're welcome.
sorry, I have no idea. But let me get Mr. Snyder for you.
谢谢
Thank you.
嗨 你的名字是
How can I help you?
喜有你叫什么名字
Hi there. What is your name?
约翰斯奈德
John Snyder.
约翰 我不知道你的名字
John. I didn't get your name.
凯莉
It's Kelly.
嗨 凯莉
Hi, Kelly.
约翰
John...
除非你想像凯莉一样
Unless you want to end up like Kelly...
你最好告诉我法兰克在哪里
I suggest you tell me where Frank Moses is right now.
快点
Now!
审问室
In interrogation.
资料里显示
I got a document right here that says that...
你对冷战有特殊的兴趣
you have a special interest in the Cold War.
我们知道你在俄罗斯那段糟糕的事
We know that back in the day, you spent a lotta time in Russia.
我想知道你所了解的"暗影行动"
I just need to know what you know about Project Nightshade.
我一无所知
I really don't know anything about it.
怎么了
What the hell is that?
袭击者来了 还有200码
Small arms gunfire, 200 yards.
看着他
Watch him.
100码
100 yards.
他们是来杀我们的
They're coming to kill us.
打开手铐
Get me outta these cuffs.
我不能 先生
I can't do that, sir.
你有钥匙 对吧
You have the key, right?
举起手来
Hands up!
50英尺
50 feet.
如果不打开手铐 他们会杀了我们
They're gonna kill us both, if you don't get me outta these cuffs.
快点
Come on.
法兰克?摩西
Frank Moses.
你可是我心目中的大英雄
Coming up through the ranks, you were my hero.
时间充足 每个人都会受不了
Given enough time, I guess eveyone cracks.
法兰克
Frank.
你是谁  我吗
Who are you?
Me?
我是政府雇用收集情报的
I'm the guy the government hires to get information.
我为求情报不择手段
And I'm allowed to use any form of torture I deem fit.
我打算折磨莎拉 直到你开口
And I will torture Sarah until you speak.
提到莎拉
Speaking of Sarah...
我喜欢看着她
I love watching her...
在浴缸里挣扎的样子
shave her legs in the tub.
令我想起了刚果叛军
Kinda reminds me of these Belgian mercs I met in the Congo.
他们为了情报而活剥人的皮肤
They would skin people alive to get them to talk.
你知道他们在哪里开始的吗
And do you know where they started?
猜猜看
Guess.
脚踝 就像你的莎拉一样
At the ankles. Just like your Sarah.
所以
So...
给我满意的答案
you either give me the information that I need to know...
否则对你的女友毫不留情
Or I'm gonna filet your girl from head to toe with no mercy.
真棒啊
Awesome.
哇
Wow.
退休真好 但是你
Pretty good for a retired guy. But are you
1 2 3 4 5 6 7
123456...
来吧 七个对一个手无寸铁的人
7 on 1 cuffed with no weapon good?
混蛋
Son of a.
向前 走 走 走
Go. Go go go!
向他开枪 但别杀了他
Shoot him, but don't kill him.
好了 杀掉他吧 散开
All right, kill him. Spray it up.
法兰克 这是你最后的机会
Frank, this is your last chance.
射击
Fire.
进去 快
Get in there! Go!
妈的
Shit.
马文
Marvin!
你把我逼疯了
You're driving me crazy!
我带钥匙来了
I brought the key.
你骗我你死了
You faked your death.
我们该走了
Gotta go.
走吧
Let's go.
快走
Gotta go.
我现在该怎么办
You have no idea what you put me through!
感谢老天爷 你没事
Thank God, you're okay.
不
No!
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
马文从那屋子把我带出来
Marvin brought me. From the house.
大家都疯了吗
Has eveybody lost their mind?
你怎么能把一个女孩带到这里
You don't bring a girl like that here.
我必须确认你没事
I had to see if you were okay.
甜心
Honey!
我以为
I thought...
什么
What?
我不是说过要低调点吗
Remember when we discussed how you were gonna lay low?
你又没有告诉我到何时为止
You don't get to tell me when to lay.
我是没有这么说
I'm not saying that.
止住 就停住
Stop. Just don't.
你现在要对我发飙吗
You're mad at me now?
你一直像对玩偶一样耍我
You treat me like a China doll.
法兰克 我能给你一点忠告吗
Frank, can I give you a little advice about women?
当然不
Absolutely not!
你扪心自问一下 什么样的女孩喜欢你这种家伙
Ask yourself, what is a girl like that doing with a guy like you?
这不是你的样子
It ain't for your looks.
我会射你 我会射掉你的肝脏
I will shoot you. I will shoot you in the liver.
A, R, D, A
A, R, D, A.
冒险 浪漫 危险
Adventure, romance, danger...
活动 你们可以是一对搭挡
activities you can share as a couple.
是因为你骗了我
It's about you lying to me.
法兰克
Frank...
我很感动你在我的葬礼上哭
I was vey touched that you cried at my funeral.
你错了
That's not true.
我根本没有哭
I didn't cy at your funeral.
我没有哭
I'm no crier.
96小时 有人在网上泄露文件
96 hours ago, somebody posted a document on the Internet...
提到我与你参与的"暗影行动"
that said you and I took part in an operation called Nightshade...
在79年时
back in '79.
所以你装死吗
That's why you fake died?
是啊 唠叨的快撑破屋顶了
Yeah. The chatter went through the roof.
所以老是很多人追你
So eveybody's after you...
问你一些你不知道的事情
for something they think you know that you don't even know at all?
喔 天啊 蜘蛛
Oh my God! Spiders!
亲爱的 你最好藏到我不知道的地方
Honey, you need to go to ground and it's best I don't know where.
我哪里也不去
Yeah, I'm not going anmhere.
只用现金 不能打电话
Cash only. No calls.
不要联系
No contacts.
谢谢 听着
Thanks. Look...
我不会躲在安乐窝里
I'm not hanging out in some bunker...
当你在外面一边与深肤色的性感女人鬼混
while you slink around and save the planet...
一边去拯救世界
with dusky international femme fatales.
深肤色的性感女人
Dusky?
肤色性感，火辣
Dark, smoldering.
我知道那是什么意思 马文
I know what it means. Marvin.
我现在的处境很危险
It's hard to be the kinda person I have to be right now...
要做的事情也很困难
and do the kinda things that I'm going to have to do...
而你在这里
while you're here.
这对我们都不是很好
This is gonna be good for us.
我们要怎么做
What are we doing?
我们面对它 科伦坡 让事情可以控制
Face it, Columbo, things were getting a little stale.
哇 妈妈在餐桌上揍了老爹
Wow. Mommy just slapped Daddy at the dinner table.
是有人在后车箱吗
Is there a human being in the trunk?
是啊
Yeah.
是谁呢 马文
Who is it? Marvin.
一个高级军事情报指挥官
He's a Senior Director of Militay Intelligence.
我已经被折磨好几天了
I've been caramelizing his onions for a couple of days.
怎么折磨呢
Caramelizing how?
迷幻药 还有一些老鼠
With three tabs of acid and a lot of rats.
妈啊
Dang!
五角大厦
THE PENTAGON
11个人被杀
11 people dead.
5个FBl的
5 FBI.
要跟国防部怎么报告
And the SecDef wants a briefing?
你是罪魁祸首
You were brought in to contain this.
冷静点
Calm down.
我无法相信事隔多年故事又重演了
I can't believe this is coming back on me after so many years.
将军 摩西和博格斯 已经被完全孤立
General, Moses and Boggs have been completely isolated.
FBl正以谋杀罪搜捕他们
The FBI is seeking them for the murders.
国安局把他们列为恐怖份子
Homeland has been informed that they are officially domestic terrorists.
这样可行吗
Is that gonna work?
是的
Yes.
问题是 如果文件在网路上流传
The problem is with that document su_acing on the Internet...
所有参加"暗影行动"的人将曝光
all the players will be coming after Nightshade.
这事可能会被史书记载
It'll open the book on this.
我去国防部一趟 我们要公诸大众
I'm calling SecDef. We need to go public.
将军
General...
任何人都不行公布
Nobody's going public.
对摩西我们要有个计划
We need a new plan for Moses.
我须要你制定一个专案
I need you to approve a specialist.
什么  CIA吗
What? CIA?
试试吧 长官 千万别交给这些人
It's been tried, sir. Didn't work so well for those guys.
韩卓佰 他是最佳人选
Han Cho Bai. He's the best.
就这样
Do it.
香港
HONG KONG
衬衫也要
Suit, too.
他很安全
He's clean.
这是干嘛
Seriously?
请坐 韩先生
Sit down, Mr. Han.
你的安全措施很完备
Your security is impressive.
此次的目标人物
A business associate.
胡里奥 瓦雷斯 费南兹
Julio Alvarez Fernandes.
他很难接近
Vey difficult to get close to.
当然 必须做得像意外事件
Of course, it must appear like an accident.
没有问题 除了一件事
Not a problem. Except for one thing.
费南兹先生 付了更多的费用
Mr. Fernandes pays better.
是
Yeah?
目标是谁
Who's the target?
你的老友 法兰克・摩西
It's an old pal of yours. Frank Moses.
他妈的老混蛋 法兰克
Karma's a bitch, Frank.
MI6总部  伦敦
HEADQUARTERS MI6 LONDON.
怎么了
What is this?
这是维基百科上的文件
There's a watchword flag on a WikiLeaks document.
它的优先代码是 1-Alpha-7
It's coded Priority One Alpha Seven.
叫做"暗影行动"
Something called Nightshade.
住嘴
Shut up!
出去
Get out.
替我找维多利亚 温斯洛
Find me Victoria Winslow.
菲利普长官
Director Philips?
我现在和某人在一起
I'm with someone right now.
我知道你很忙
Keeping busy, I see.
只是些肮脏的工作而已
Idle hands do the Devil's work.
是啊
Yes.
我知道你能接近法兰克・摩西
I understand you can get close to Frank Moses.
是的
Yes.
MI6有个任务给你
MI6 has a iob for you.
如果你想活命 就必须接受
If you want to stay alive, you're going to accept it.
是时候选边站了 维多利亚
It's time to choose sides, Victoria.
谁教你们这些的
Where do they teach you guys this stuff?
使用手册
Manuals, mostly.
有些事是不用教的
Some of this stuff you just can't teach.
哇
Wow.
很酷啊
Isn't this cool?
我们一起执行任务
We're on a mission together.
你知道吗 有很多人想干掉我们
Do you have any idea how many people are tying to kill us?
我们都知道这是你的地盘
We both know this is where you belong.
就在这里
Right here. In the thick of it.
她说得对 法兰克
Pussy Cat's right, Frank.
走吧
Here we go.
脚下留神
Watch your step.
帮帮忙
Come on!
你从哪里拿的
Where did you get this?
马文
Marvin.
你给她枪
You gave her a gun?
这里是美国
It is America.
每个人都可以有枪
Eveyone else has a gun.
她不会使用它
She has no idea what to do with this.
我知道怎么用
I know exactly what to do with it.
你不能给小猫一把枪
You don't give fire to a kitten.
为什么不给她一些炸药
Why don't you just give her some dynamite?
手枪没有开保险吗
No exernal safety on the Sig?
告诉他我对你说的
Tell him what you told me.
在冷战的时候
At the height of the Cold War...
暗影行动是一个美国将军制定的
Nightshade was cooked up by a rogue US General...
第一目标是对抗苏联
as a first strike capability against the Soviets.
就这样 我可以走了吗
That's it. Can I go?
想要再来点辣椒吗
You want a little pepper with that?
冷战时期
At the height of the Cold War...
大量设备走私到莫斯科
a megaton yield device was smuggled into Moscow...
用外交邮件 一件一件的
in diplomatic pouches, piece by piece...
可是武器消失不见了 就这样
and then the weapon was lost. That's it.
你在莫斯科弄丢了武器
You lost a nuke in Moscow?
那科学家叫 爱德华贝利 就是他
The scientist was Edward Bailey. That's it.
怎么了
What?
我犯了个错
I made a mistake.
爱德华贝利是个天才物理学家
Edward Bailey was a genius physicist...
冷战时最大的武器是他制造的
who built some of the greatest stuff during the Cold War.
中子炸弹 粒子束武器 神经毒气
Neutron bombs, particle beam weapons, nerve gas.
特别是神经毒气
Excellent nerve gas.
他是暗杀界的闪亮之星
He was a rock star of conceptual mass killing.
他们称他为"达芬奇之死"
They called him "The Da Vinci of Death".
我们那时执行武器安检
We were the security detail...
试图把它安全移出莫斯科
assigned to getting him in and out of Moscow safely.
发生什么事了
What happened?
我们以为万无一失时
We thought he was secure.
苏联军队在一辆炸弹汽车抓到了他
The Soviets got him with a car bomb.
都是我的错
It was my fault.
他死了
He's dead.
逃跑还是战斗
Run or fight?
我们得到的只是维基百科的网页
All we've got is this WikiLeaks page off the Internet.
来自巴黎的IP
Out of a Paris IP.
巴黎的任何一个人
Paris could be anybody.
等等 回去前面去
Wait. Scroll back down for a second.
那是什么
What is that?
咖啡污点
Coffee stain?
酒
Wine.
青蛙
Frog.
怎么了
What?
没事
We're okay.
你的电话
Your number.
是
Yeah.
MI6刚刚给我一个任务去杀你
MI6 has just given me a contract to kill you.
核子武器的罪魁祸首
Apparently, you're guilty of nuclear terrorism, murder...
第一首要的通缉犯
and you're number one on Interpol's Most Wanted.
你怎么说呢
What did you say?
我说"好啊"
I said "Yes."
你知道报酬优厚 我不做别人也会做的
The money's good. And if I don't do it, somebody else will.
你要知道美国也派人在搜寻你
You should know the Americans are sending someone also.
谁呢
Who?
韩
Han.
很糟糕 不是吗
It's bad, isn't it?
那是马文吗
Is that Marvin?
是的  还有莎拉
Yes. And Sarah.
帮我向她问好
Send them my love.
他们把我快逼疯了
They're driving me crazy.
马文给了她一支枪
Marvin gave her a gun.
有子弹吗
Was it loaded?
有
Yes!
你能控制住吗
Are you being controlling?
不行
No!
你要把握机会建立好关系
You have to take chances in a relationship.
你必须获得支持
You have to be supportive.
我不需要她加入 我要她安全
I don't need her to fit in. I just need her to be safe.
租片"热舞十七"然后告诉她你爱她
Just rent "Dirty Dancing", tell her you love her.
知道吗 在活着时享受生活是很重要的
It's important to enjoy life while you still can.
维多利亚刚从MI6接了杀我们的任务
Victoria just accepted a contract from MI6 to kill all 3 of us.
她不会这么做 对吗
You don't think she'd do that, do you?
她是我们的朋友
She's a friend.
你笨蛋啊 你没接过杀朋友的任务吗
Are you stupid? You never took a contract out to kill a friend?
她告诉我们还警告我们
She called to give us fair warning.
走吧 还有一件事
Come on. There's one more thing.
韩会第一个过来的
Han just went number one.
为什么我们不把蛋蛋放入蜂蜜里
Why don't they just dip our balls in honey...
然后再扔到蚂蚁窝里呢
and stake us to an ant farm?
来吧
Come on.
哇
Whoa!
疯狂的老混蛋
Crazy old bastard.
法兰克 你觉得老了吗
Frank, do you feel old?
没什么感觉
Not really.
我也是
Me neither.
我想也许有时候很疯狂
Crazy sometimes, I guess.
谁是韩
Who's Han?
一个韩国小子
Korean. Counter intel.
法兰克抓了他 害他坐好几年牢
Frank put him in jail for a few years.
我们应该害怕他吗
We should be super scared of him?
是的 他是世界最顶级的杀手
Yes. He is the best contract killer in the world.
我找到他们的旧名 已经20年没用了
I've got a hit off an old alias, silent for almost 20 years.
进入查看页面
He's dodging watch lists.
搞定了 九点坐私人飞机从泰特波罗飞往巴黎
Bingo. Private flight to Paris scheduled for 0900 out of Teterboro.
查明宾馆 找出白天和晚间的值班经理
Find their hotel. Get blueprints and workups on the day and night managers.
叫文森在着陆时见我们
Have Vance meet us on the ground.
新泽西 泰特波罗
TETERBORO, NEW JERSEY
他们在一楼 两间套房
They're 1 floor down. 2 adioining rooms.
到处都布置监视器
Surveillance is almost up and running.
比我想像容易多了
This is going to be easier than I thought.
你好 请说
Hello. Speaking.
是的
Yes.
他们在哪里
Where are they?
他们来过 一点时还叫了客房服务
They were here. They ordered room service at 1 o'clock.
你说飞机离开是什么意思
What do you mean "The plane is prepped"?
我想有人偷了你的飞机
I think someone stole your plane.
我真的要把他杀了
I'm really going to enioy killing him.
给我一支火力最大的枪
Get me a gun that really hurts.
这家伙实力如何
How good is this guy?
韩是世界顶级的杀手
Han is the best contract killer in the world.
法兰克应该是十分幸运了
Frank is in some vey deep dog doo.
他不会杀我的
He's not gonna kill me.
是啊 没有人杀得了法兰克・摩西
Yeah. Nobody kills Frank Moses.
没错
Right!
他实在不讨人喜欢 他虐待他一阵子
The people he really doesn't like, he tortures for a long time first.
我们能不能集中精神来抓青蛙呢
Can we just focus on tying to catch The Frog?
捉捕和运输的计划行动是什么
What's the action plan for target acquisition and rendition?
马文
Marvin?
别教她一些乱七八糟的
Quit teaching her stuff!
真棒
Nice.
你觉得世界上最贵的酒怎么样
What do you think the most expensive bottle of wine in the world costs?
伊甘酒庄 1847年的
Chateau d'Yquem 1847.
世界上也许只有五六瓶 非常稀有
Maybe 5, 6 bottles left in the world. It's pretty pricey.
或许我应该弄一瓶来抓青蛙
Maybe we should get a bottle and Try to catch The Frog with it.
巴黎
PARIS
天啊 真是浪漫
My God, this is so romantic!
来吧 低着头
Come here. Keep your head down.
但我们必须去圣路易吃冰淇淋
But we have to go to the le Saint Louis for gelato.
我不这么认为
I don't think so.
是吗 那么
Really? What about the...
法兰克 这是
Frank, is that?
你好 法兰克
Hello, Frank.
你以前见过他吗
Have you seen her since?
没有
Nope.
天啊 我好想念你啊
God, I've missed you.
她是谁
Who is she?
冤家
Trouble.
最近如何
How are things?
啊 法兰克 最近如何
Yeah, Frank, how are things?
莎拉
Sarah...
这位是卡嘉
This is Katia.
你好
Yeah. Hi.
我有话要跟你说 现在
I need to speak with you. Immediately.
到底是怎么回事
What the hell was that?
卡嘉 反俄罗斯组织人员
Katja Petrokovich. Russian Counter Intelligence.
我想我们应该听听她要说什么
I think we should hear what she has to say.
法兰克
Frank...
你不了解的
You don't know the half of it.
她在法兰克年轻时
She and Frank were young.
他还不知道她为俄罗斯工作
He didn't have the slightest idea she was working for the Russians.
她是法兰克・摩西的克星
She's Frank Moses' kyptonite.
我喜欢你头光秃秃的
I like you with no hair.
光头男比较性感
Bald men are so sey. Virile.
哇
Wow.
她很漂亮 你在哪里捡的 内布拉斯加吗
She's cute. Where did you find her? Nebraska?
堪萨斯
Kansas.
那么你想告诉我什么呢
So what was it you wanted to talk to me about?
我还是相信美国没有计划
I would like to believe that the US didn't plant...
在莫斯科设置大规模杀伤武器 但我不这么认为
a weapon of mass destruction in Moscow. But I don't.
你来巴黎做什么
Why are you in Paris?
我们每年秋天都来 因为天气不错
We come evey fall for Strike Season and for the weather.
美国似乎认为你是恐怖份子
The US seems to think you're nuclear terrorists.
俄罗斯方面想掌控全局
Russia wants complete access.
现在你要同意 或者把你交给美国政府
You agree now or I'll hand you over to the US government.
我们能直接杀了她吗
Can't we just kill her?
不好意思
Excuse me for one second.
我们能谈谈吗
Can I talk to you?
什么 哦 当然
What? Uh huh. Sure thing.
我很震惊
I was shocked.
我知道 她把你的牙齿舔得很干净
I know. She was kinda counting your teeth with her tongue.
是啊 有点
A little, yeah.
她现在能走了吗
Can she go now?
我们别无选择 我们需要她的帮忙
We don't really have a choice. We need her to help us.
我发誓 我们之间没什么
I promise there is nothing between us.
长官 这里什么都没有
No, sir. This guy's not giving us anything.
网站已经被移除了
Website's been scrubbed.
NSA拦截到了 从克里姆林宫发到巴黎的信号
NSA intercepted a dispatch to the Kremlin from Paris.
摩西在找叫"青蛙"的人
Moses is going after someone called "The Frog".
"青蛙"
The Frog.
他们叫他"青蛙" 难道他是法国人
So they call him "The Frog" because he's French?
不 他在KGB总部的供水系统下毒
No. He poisoned the water supply at KGB headquarters...
用亚马逊的毒青蛙
with the Amazon tree frog poison.
他一定收集了这些小东西好几年
He must have been wiping those little tree humpers for years.
毒死了600人 带走了我们的机密
Incapacitated 1600 people and left with evey secret we had.
这家伙有卖情报的运气
The guy makes a fortune selling information.
他知道美国方面不会碰他
He knows so much even the US won't touch him.
最难的是无法活捉他
The hard part is gonna be taking him alive.
很好
Superb.
酒归酒
Wine is wine.
我要买美国防御协议
I want to buyAmerican air defense protocols.
为什么恐怖份子不懂欣赏葡萄酒
Why is it terrorists never appreciate Burgundy?
我可不认为你懂得怎么处理
I don't think you know who you're dealing with.
竞标价格
PLACE BID
出售
SOLD
确定是他 是青蛙
Confirmed. It's him. It's the Frog.
记住别看着他的眼睛 好吗
Just don't look at him, right?
自然一点
Just act natural.
不管怎样 别看着他的眼睛
And don't look him right in the eyes.
收到
Check.
记住 别看着他
Remember, don't look right at him.
马文 你没事吧
Marvin, you All right?
好
Yeah.
把她带离开这里
Get her outta here.
何时
When?
现在
Now!
弄辆车子
Get a car!
是那个吗
Is that?
拦住他们
Cut them off!
这不是个好主意
This is not a good idea!
她不会是第一个先到的
She's not gonna get there first!
走人行道
Sidewalk!
小心路边
Watch the curb!
很好
Yes!
追上他 笨蛋
Happy trails, bozo!
你不认为我们应该...
Don't you think we should let...
闭上你的嘴 马文
Shut your pie hole, Marvin!
你不认为我们应该让...
Don't you think we should let...
安静
Hush!
来了
Incoming!
混蛋 人行道
Bastard! Sidewalk!
这是什么
What the?
她没事的
She's fine.
追上他
Got him.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
捉到他了
Got him.
她在干什么
Look! What is she doing?
我在乞讨
I'm begging.
是啊 我得到了
Yeah, yeah. I got this.
我得到了
I so got this.
我非常讨厌她
I hate her so much.
你是在浪费时间
You're wasting your time!
你将无法想像你会有多后悔
You're going to regret this more than you can possibly imagine.
你知道我们是谁吗
You know who we are?
是啊 当然
Yes, of course.
告诉我们有关"暗影行动"
Tell us about Nightshade.
你认为我会屈服你的暴行吗
You think I'm going to roll over for you hegemonic...
米奇老鼠热爱美国吗
Mickey Mouse loving Americans?
别提米奇老鼠了
Leave Mickey out of it.
1947年 P trus的
1947 P trus?
是的 那个很...
Yes. That one's rather...
天啊
God's sake!
等等 那一瓶
Wait wait wait! That bottle!
我们要怎么找到
How do we find it?
永远找不到
Never!
"暗影行动"是个疯狂的计划
Nightshade was the plot of lunatics.
我曾经像你一样
I used to be like you.
受意识和恐惧的驱动
Driven by ideology and fear...
对这美丽的世界没有爱
with no love of what's beautiful in the world.
我不能相信像你这样的畜生
I can't trust animals like you!
随你怎么做
Do what you will.
死亡很简单
Death is easy.
但这不是目的 主要是过程
It's not about the destination.it's about the journey.
死亡在俄国是一门艺术
Death is an art form in Russia.
有很多方法让一个人开口
There are so many ways to take a man to bits.
我们从剥下他的脸皮开始 压住他
Shall we start with a Chechen facelift? Hold him down!
不要 住手
Stop! Stop it!
这就是我们的风格
This is how we do it.
求你了 你这么勇敢
Please. You're so brave.
但是你必须明白
But you have to understand...
我们这么做有正当的理由 还有
we're doing this for the right reasons. And this...
这不值得你去卖命
This isn't worth your life.
你一定有活下来的目标
You must have something to live for.
艺术
Art.
美酒
Wine.
女人
Women?
嘿
Hey.
救救我们
Help us.
我们需要这份情报
We need this information.
你会帮助我们救救这个世界 求你了
You'll be helping us save the world. Please.
你 我会帮助的
You, I'll help.
抱歉
Excuse me.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你去死吧
And you can suck it.
宝贝 亲爱的
Baby? Honey?
真的吗 你这样勾搭上的
Seriously? You hooked up with that?
女人啊
What a woman.
那是同样一件吗
Is that the same dress?
你看起来是一样的吗
They look the same to you?
没有人称我是"法兰克・摩西的克星"
No one ever called me Frank Moses' kyptonite.
法兰克对你太着迷了
Frank's crazy about you.
我从没看过他那么害怕失去了你
I've never seen him afraid of anything except losing you.
如果我毁了他的人生怎么办
What if I'm ruining his life?
法兰克是个单纯生物 他的需求很简单
Frank is a vey simple creature with vey simple needs.
就是杀戮
It's killing...
进食
eating...
做爱
sexing...
进食
eating...
杀戮 我猜是吧
Killing, I guess.
什么意思呢
What's your point?
我无法相信你吻了这只"青蛙"
I can't believe you kissed The Frog.
我可亲吻过很多"青蛙"呢
Well, I've kissed a lot of frogs.
我有东西给你
I got something for ya.
是什么
What is it?
"青蛙"秘密保险柜的钥匙
The key to The Frog's security deposit box.
在哪里
From?
里昂信贷银行
Credit Lyonnais.
宝贝 我有个请求
Baby, I have a request.
今晚与我一起出去吃晚餐如何
How would you feel about going out to dinner with me tonight?
毕竟这里是巴黎
It is Paris, after all.
是啊 好啊
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
待在这里 我马上回来
Stay here. I'll be right back.
我需要你 法兰克
I need you, Frank.
这可不是好时机
It's not a good time.
我们有个老同事说有重要的情报
One of our old assets has some real information.
他需要马上见我们
He needs to meet with us right now.
不行
Nah.
法兰克 你在干什么 她是你的克星
Frank, what are you doing? She's kyptonite.
我会处理好的
I'll handle it.
你肯定吗
Are you sure?
是
Yeah.
不太好吧 还有工作呢 不是开玩笑的
It's not okay. It's just some work. No, it's not fun.
走 去和斯维特兰娜干活吧
Go. You and Svetlana work it out.
我保证会回来一起吃晚餐的
I promise you that I will be back in time for dinner.
我会回来的
I'll be back.
照顾她的安全
Keep her safe.
我们怎么了 法兰克
What happened to us, Frank?
嗯
Well...
你背叛我 你坑了我 你打算杀了我
You betrayed me. You set me up. Tried to kill me.
我是打算杀了你
I tried to kill you.
这是最好的机会 不是吗
They were good times, weren't they?
知道吗 如果你要我背叛我的国家 你知道我会的
If you'd asked me to betray my county, you know I would have.
是的 夫人
Yes, madam.
天啊
My God.
知道吗 我见过你们
You know, I looked you up once.
在洛杉矶的屋子里
You were in a bungalow in Los Angeles.
屋前满满的玫瑰
There were roses out in front.
但我失去了我的自信
But I lost my nerve.
那么你想怎样呢
So what do you want?
和你都只是工作关系 规则
It was all about work with you. Rules.
不是规则
Not rules.
是对与错
Right and wrong.
违抗命令对我来说很难
It's harder for me not to follow orders.
我可以不顾个人感受
Despite my personal feelings.
但感觉与对错无关
But feelings don't matter any more than right or wrong.
命令至关重要
Orders matter.
命令
Orders?
俄国会操纵这里的一切
Russia will handle things from here.
我要拿走钥匙
I'm taking the key.
我不会让这种事发生的
I can't let that happen.
不会吗
No?
我的胳臂失去知觉了
I can't feel my arms.
享受堪萨斯吧
Enioy Kansas.
他失去知觉了
He's out.
或许会清醒过来
He might be awake.
很好 那就会有感觉了
Good. So he can feel it.
在你整个生涯中
Did you ever, ever in your entire career...
有没有什么让你变得麻木
let yourself get drugged?
我就是不喜欢她
I just don't like her!
现在她有钥匙了
And now she has the key!
她没有钥匙  她有钥匙
She doesn't have the key. She has a key.
什么
What?
我知道她会让他中计
I knew she would play him like a banjo at an Ozark hoedown.
所以我保留钥匙了
So I have the key.
水
Water.
我还要多久才能离开
How long was I out for?
有一些是他的
Some of it's his.
马文
Et tu, Marvin?
风格是生活中唯一不变的
Style is the only constant in life.
我们来巴黎不是渡假的
We didn't come to Paris on vacation.
我以为你是来巴黎"血拼"的
Shopping's what I thought you did in Paris...
用你男朋友的钱
with your boyriend's money...
当你在等他的时候
while you're waiting for him...
在沉迷中醒过来
to wake up from being taken down...
他的前任俄国女婊子
by his skanky, slutty, Russian bitch ex girlfriend.
非常感谢
So thanks.
感谢你所有的恭维
Thanks for the compliment for the fur.
告诉我我穿这条裙子很好看
For telling me that I look nice in my dress.
让我感觉真的很好
It makes me feel really good.
也让我感觉你也很好
And it makes me feel very loving towards you also.
为什么他对我这么做
Why is she doing this to me?
我们可以叫计程车
We can get a taxi over here.
听着 我有些事要跟你说
Listen, I gotta tell you something.
你需要把你的感受告诉周围的人
You have to share your feelings to evolve your relationship.
虽然刚开始很别扭
Even if it seems uncomfortable at first.
譬如你被困在火海里
Say you're pinned down in a firefight.
如果你待在原地就会烧死 知道吗
If you stay where you are, you're gonna die. Okay?
那么 你怎么做
So what do you do?
逃跑啊
Make the run.
对 你必须跑
Yes. You have got to make the run...
跑到安全的地方
to emotional safety.
你死了吗 摩西
You dead yet, Moses?
还没
Not yet.
我的飞机在哪里
Where's my plane?!
在我屁股里
In my ass!
在巴黎郊区的机场
It's in an airport outside of Paris.
你在说什么 闭嘴
What are you? Shut up!
离开这里
Let's get outta here.
马文
Marvin?
是
Yeah?
你袋子里的炸弹做什么用的
Is that a stick of dynamite in your pocket?
是用在紧急情况下的
Yeah, but I'm saving it for an emergency.
这就是紧急情况 对吗
This is kind of an emergency, isn't it?
里昂信贷银行
CREDIT LYONNAIS BANK
巴黎
PARIS
我给他的钥匙是用来
The key I gave her is connected to...
开启保险柜的 恐怖份子都很想要
a particularly nasty terrorist cell and their safe deposit box.
法国人正在紧急通缉她
The French take this kinda thing pretty seriously.
够了
That's enough.
把我放下 快点
Put me down now! Now!
好吧
All right.
我们的快点行动 莫斯科一小时内就会把她弄出来
We gotta move quickly, Moscow will have her out within the hour.
为了迈克的爱
For the love of Mike.
好吧
All right.
我没有跟你说话
I'm still not talking to you.
这是MI6关于"暗影行动"的报告
This is an MI6 report on Project Nightshade.
关于行动装置的地点
It's about the operative that placed the device.
他们把他暂时关到ICE
They took him into custody and put him on ICE.
什么是ICE
What's ICE?
抓进去就无法逃离了
Incarcerate, Cannot Execute.
他们会把谁关在ICE待32年
Who would they keep on ICE for 32 years?
来吧 该走了
Come on. Gotta go.
英格兰
ENGLAND
她怎么可能发现我们呢
How could she have possibly found us?
因为我告诉她 我们要来了
'Cause I called her and told her we were coming.
我无法承受事情不确定的压力
I couldn't take the pressure of not knowing.
为什么她不朝我们开枪
Why isn't she shooting at us?
那会给我们多24小时时间
That should buy us 24 hours.
哈罗 亲爱的
Hello, sweetie.
下次你要干这种事 先告诉我一声
The nex time you 2 make a plan like this, at least let me in on it.
你们要牺牲我
You're compromising me.
谁知道那些女孩要供出你
Who knows what some girl is gonna squeeze out of you?
你从哪里弄到这些尸体的
Where'd you get the bodies?
我的冷冻库
My freezer.
来吧 醒醒
Come on. Wake up.
到底怎么回事
Yeah? What the hell's going on?
长官
Sir?
从"青蛙"那里得到什么情报
Get anything from The Frog?
没有 他在我们询问前服了一种毒药
No, he took some sorta poison before we really talked.
我认为他现在什么也不会说
I don't think he's gonna say anything now.
你必须去找摩西和博格斯
You've got to find Moses and Boggs.
别担心 我正在路上
Don't wory. I'm on the trail.
伦敦
LONDON
在右边 你看到的是出名的伦敦塔
On your right, you see the famous Tower of London.
我们会穿过塔底下
And shortly, we'll be passing under the Tower Bridge.
一个堡垒
It's a fortress.
它是秘密关押罪犯的监狱
It's an asylum for the criminally insane.
他在ICE里面
He's in the ICE unit.
那是MI6 A级安保地点
That's an MI6 Alpha Level secure facility...
深藏在那座大楼中
buried deep within that building.
就像监狱中的监狱
It's like a prison within a prison.
我们要怎么进去
How are we gonna get in there?
他想要我的头
She wants my head!
这是天主教的阴谋
It's a Papist plot.
那个苏格兰贱人皇后 他想要我的头
It's that bitch May Queen of Scots. She wants my head.
你在干什么 不
What are you doing? No!
给我叫塞西尔 我才是苏格兰皇后
Get me Cecil. I'm the Queen of England!
不要带我去城堡
Don't take me to the Tower!
我会砍下你的头的 婊子
I'll have your head for this, you bitch!
不 不
No! No!
头戴王冠可不简单啊
"Uneasy lies the head that wears the crown."
他们所有的人都想要反抗我
They're plotting against me. All of them.
这才是个好皇后
There's a good queen.
别说了 老妖怪
Stuff it, you old bat.
谢了
Thank you.
如果不介意 别再叫我老妖怪了
Not so much the "old", if you don't mind.
我觉得这个很不错
I think it was really good.
我以为在引导Bette Davis呢
I thought I was channeling Bette Davis.
早安 琼斯医生想要看一下17号患者
Good morning. Dr. Jones to see prisoner number 17, please.
琼斯医生 来自MI6的吗
Dr. Jones? Are you with MI6?
当然 但不再是了
Certainly, not anymore.
电脑表单上没有你的名字
I don't seem to have you on my list.
这东西不好使用 为什么
Bloody thing's not working. Why's that?
你应该使用...
You're supposed to use.
趴在地板上 很好
Lay down on the ground.
121病房 就是那里
Number 121. There it is.
法兰克
Frank!
你们是谁 参观的吗 找谁呢
Who are you? You're visitors? Who are you looking for?
我们喜欢参观者 不是吗 伙伴们
We love having visitors, don't we, fellas?
贝利教授
Dr. Bailey?
Doctor Bailey?
是啊 不然还会有谁呢
Yes. Who did you expect to find here?
教授
Sir...
怎么
What?
我看到你死了
I saw you die.
看到我死了 他是谁
Saw me die? Who is he?
法兰克
Frank?
法兰克・摩西 我亲爱的朋友 你好吗
Frank Moses, my dear fellow! How are you, old sport?
很高兴见到你 欢迎你来
So glad to see you. So glad you came by.
我们期待很久了 不是吗
We've been expecting you. Haven't we, fellas?
天啊 你怎么这么老了
My God, why are you so old?
老天啊
Good lord!
教授
Sir...
什么
What?
你已经被关32年了
You've been locked up here for 32 years.
来吧 法兰克 开什么玩笑 玩一下
Frankie, you've gotta be kidding me. Come on, put 'em up.
32年 怎么可能 你叫什么名字
32 years. How exraordinay. Who are you?
维多利亚
Victoria.
维多利亚 你应该看看这个 列宁的 "国家与革命"
Victoria! You should read this. Lenin. " State and Revolution."
快乐的时光 斯大林肯定会搞砸的
Jolly good time. Stalin got it wrong, of course.
我们要去哪里呢 法兰克 歌剧院吗
Where are we going, Frank? Are you taking us to the opera?
我们要去哪里 我们都喜欢歌剧 不是吗
Is that where we're going? We love the opera, don't we, fellas?
有香槟和草莓的歌剧院
The opera and the champagne and the strawberries all round.
抱歉 亲爱的 再请问你的名字
sorry, my dear, what is your name again?
维多利亚
Victoria.
抱歉 这是药物作用 影响我的记忆
sorry, it's the drugs they're feeding me, it's my short term memory.
一种让我平静而又无害的东西
Something that's meant to keep us peaceful or harmless!
反正就在附近 但我又不知道在哪里
Anmay, it's around here somewhere, but I don't know where.
贝利教授 我们需要你的帮助
Dr. Bailey, we need your help.
你记得"暗影行动"吗
Do you remember Nightshade?
抱歉 我在找烟斗和圣克里斯托弗奖章
I'm looking for my pipe and my St. Christopher medallion.
那些年轻人把它给别人了 都是些小孩
Boys gave it to someone. They were little boys.
大概跑到哪里去了
And now it's gone somehow.
喔 糟糕
Oh shit!
法兰克 我在这里
Hey, Frankie, I'm over here.
我找到了 一直在我的口袋里
I found it. It was in my pocket the whole time.
尽管我找不到烟斗了 还好在这里
I couldn't find my damn pipe, though. But here it is.
抱歉 亲爱的 你刚才问我什么
sorry, my dear, what was the question you asked me?
你记得"暗影行动"吗
Do you remember Nightshade?
我记得那是一种炸弹
Vaguely. It was some kind of a bomb, I believe.
有人正在找它 想要使用它
People are looking for that weapon. People who want to use it.
亲爱的 我了解 相信我
Oh dear. Yes, I do understand of course. Believe me.
我为美国制造了很多东西
But I made many things for the Americans and...
"暗影行动"是最吓人的杰作
Nightshade turned out to be a bit of a nightmare.
与众不同 又非常危险
It was quite different. Turned out to be too dangerous.
所以他们自然要把我关在这里
So naturally, they had to lock me up in this place.
即使他们对我做了这些事后 我觉得这很正常
And after what they did to me, I think it's perfectly natural...
我警告过他们要滚远点
I tell them all to go F off!
MI6想制造贝利死亡的谎言
MI6 tried to fake Bailey's death?
为什么 他们想隐瞒什么
Why? What are they hiding?
你得走了 他们发现你了
You're gonna have to go. You're gonna have to go find out.
他们想杀了我的
You know they're gonna Ty and kill me.
到俄国再找你
I'll call you from Russia.
维护7号桥
Maintenance to Bridge 7.
安全系统出现紧急状况
We got a breach in Maximum Security.
保全
Secure!
什么事那么重要
What's so important?
我刚从MI6得到消息 爱德华贝利还活着 并已经逃走了
I just heard from my source at MI6 that Edward Bailey's alive and on the run.
这不可能
That's not possible.
这比想像中的麻烦还大
This is bigger than a rogue General and his unexploded ordinance.
我还有什么不知道的
What don't I know?
游戏改变了
The game has changed.
贝利知道的事情太危险了
The things Bailey knows are too dangerous.
如果贝利或者暗影行动落入恐怖份子 将有数万人会丧生
If Bailey or Nightshade fall into terrorist hands, millions will die.
喔 天啊 这是真的
Holy shit, it's real.
除非我们销毁它，那个武器正在莫斯科中心地区
Unless we secure it, that weapon's going off in the middle of Moscow.
这就是我们最好的应急措施
Right now, that's our best case scenario.
俄罗斯
RUSSIA
伙计们
Guys?
欢迎 我的朋友们
Welcome, my friends.
传言是真的 你还活着
So, it is true. You're alive.
告诉我 是谁操控的
Tell me, then, where is this device?
谁
Who?
我们在努力
Work in progress.
我从来没有想过
I never thought I'd be smuggling...
带法兰克・摩西到俄罗斯中心地区去
Frank Moses into the heart of Mother Russia.
我也是
Me, neither.
在我忘记前 这里有点小东西
Before I forget. A little something.
如果你被抓了或韩抓了你
If you are caught or Han catches you...
服药自杀是最好的选择
suicide pill is a much better option than what you face.
就算死 也会死得很漂亮
You die with Russian smile on.
祝好运
Good luck.
贝利教授
Mr. Bailey.
法兰克
Yes, Frank?
有什么方式可以告诉我们核武器在哪里
Is there any way you could tell us where you hid the nuclear weapon?
这些堡垒 可真是漂亮啊
Look at all those cows. They're beautiful.
堡垒
Yeah.
母牛
Cows?
嗨！
Hi! Yoo hoo!
情况不妙
That's not good.
莫斯科
MOSCOW
我们被跟踪了 法兰克
We have eyes on, Frank.
我的飞机在哪里
Where's my plane?
他们雇我来杀你
They paid me to kill you.
没有说要保留全尸
They didn't say I had to do it all at once.
别动
FREEZE
把手放头上
HANDS ON YOUR HEAD
波士奇呼叫 这里有警察受伤
THIS IS OFFICER BOESKY. OFFICER DOWN
我们需要医生
WE NEED MEDICALASSISTANCE
别动 把手放头上
FREEZE, HANDS ON YOUR HEAD
他怎么了
What's wrong with him?
哇
Wow.
这是什么地方
What is this place?
我第一个安全屋
My first safe house.
邻家女孩 是从1984年开始的
Untouched, since 1984.
河豚毒
Fugu poison?
那可是剧毒
Fugu poison is deadly stuff. Terrible death.
看到了吗 XKG毒气 我发明的
This little gizmo? XKG gas. I invented it.
我们想在61年刺杀古巴总统卡斯楚
We tried to take out old Fidel Castro in '61 in Cuba.
但是没有奏效
That didn't work though.
选一个吧 法兰克
Any tea, Frank?
为什么韩那么讨厌你
Why does Han hate you so much?
从小时候起他就讨厌我
Not enough hugs as a child.
法兰克盗取了国家的机密
Frank framed him for stealing state secrets.
然后从一个优秀情报员
So he went from being a highly decorated counter intel officer...
变成可怕的杀手
to being a pariah.
最讽刺的是 法兰克
What's ironic is that Frank...
总在刺杀时出现了些状况
actually created the circumstances for his own death.
很戏剧性
It's poetic.
我还没有死
I ain't dead yet.
你在吃那东西
Should you eat that?
安全吗
Is that safe?
它还是在  过期之前
It's before they had that, you know, "sell by" date stuff.
所以你见过卡斯楚了
Did you get to meet Castro?
谁
Who?
你见过卡斯楚了
Did you get to meet Castro?
当然 在甘乃迪死后的二星期
Yes, I did. About 2 weeks after Kennedy was assassinated.
顺便说一下 法兰克
Talking of which, Frank...
我开始记起来我是谁了
I'm starting to remember more and more who I am...
我以前干什么的 还有我制造的武器
and who I was and the weapons I made.
天啊 太神奇了
My God, it really is amazing.
MI6的人都是好人 上帝保佑他们
How efficiently those boys from MI6, God bless 'em...
但他们确实遗弃了我们 不是吗 老兄
But they really do throw us away. Don't they, old sport?
我们年龄大了 大概吧
When we're no longer convenient, I suppose.
好像我们没有把最好的时光献给它
As though we'd never given them the best years of our lives.
真是个天大的笑话
Bit of a ioke, really.
没错 真奇怪
Yes, vey strange.
你记得"暗影行动"在哪里吗
Do you remember where Nightshade is?
抱歉 亲爱的
I'm sorry, my dear?
你记得"暗影行动"在哪里吗
Do you remember where Nightshade is?
当然记得
Oh, yes.
好像是穿过这里
This feels right.
我来过这里 我肯定
It's around here somewhere. I'm sure this time.
一切都变不一样了
Eveything looks different completely.
可能是穿过这里
Maybe it's over here.
一小时了
It's been hours.
就是这里
Yeah, this is it.
我们到了
Here we are.
你觉得这事和吉米周有什么关系
How are those Jimmy Choos working out for you?
入口在上面
The entrance is up there.
约翰爸爸
PAPA JOHN'S
谁是约翰爸爸
Who's Papa John?
刚听到的
It's new.
去哪里的入口
Entrance to what?
穿过古陵寝的秘密通道
Secret tunnels through the old catacombs.
这曾是布里滋涅夫情妇的秘密通道
Brezhnev used it to sneak his mistress in.
在那里吗
In where?
在那里
In there.
克里姆林宫
The Kremlin?
核弹在克里姆林宫
The weapon is in the Kremlin?
那是他们唯一不会检查的地方
It's the one place they wouldn't look.
天啊 你能让它保暖吗
Jesus.Do you mind keeping it warm?
你不知道你所做造成了多大破坏
You have no idea the damage you've done.
你居然把自己人关了32年
You kept one of our own locked up for 32 years.
我要让世界维持和平
I have kept the world safe.
如果核武落入不法份子手中呢
If that weapon falls into the wrong hands.
武器
The weapon?
你真是什么都不懂
You haven't the slightest idea.
你要马上联系摩西 他不知道是陷阱
You must let me call Moses. He doesn't know what he's walking into.
你已经有过这机会的 都结束了
You've had your chance. It's over.
我很抱歉 维多利亚
I'm sorry, Victoria.
去你妈的抱歉
sorry, my ass.
他们说你是这里的传奇
They say you're a legend around here.
但是 我...
I've...
我从没有听说过
I've never heard of you.
一定要说些我以前的事
Must have been a bit before my time.
现在听说过我了吧
You've heard of me now.
他们怎么检测不到核弹的幅射呢
How is it possible they never picked up the radiation signature from that bomb?
这个问题很好
That's the million dollar question.
嘿 伙计 这是新的
Hey, gang. This is new.
墙的后面是什么呢
What do you think is behind that wall?
应该是俄国人
I think Russians.
要是有人发现这个洞 我们就死定了
If anybody sees that hole, we're dead.
我需要你解除核武装置
I'm gonna need you to help me to disarm the weapon.
要有人在外面把风
Somebody's gotta guard the door.
不
No.
但是
But...
你需要这个
You'll need this.
主席
COMRADE GENERAL
这是20分钟前被带进红场的
THIS IS RED SQUARE 20 MINUTES AGO
检查建筑物 军队戒备
SECURITY SWEEP THE BUILDING, GET THE ARMY NOW
再来一次  是的
One more time.
很好 是什么意思
Great. What does that mean?
瓦斯外泄 工作人员很快就会来了
"Gas leak. Maintenance is coming."
很好 然后他们就会走
Good. And then they'll move on.
如果不走呢
What if they don't?
想要支枪吗
Want a gun?
好啊
Yes.
不能拿枪
No gun.
别动
Just don't move.
你是安全警卫
You're a security guard.
别笑 你不能笑
Don't smile. You can't smile.
只要不离开岗位就行了 好吗
You never leave your post. Okay?
很好
Nice.
两个摄影头 这里和这里
2 shots, here and here.
把他拖进去 来一个杀一个
Drag the body in there and repeat as necessay.
不安全吗
No safety.
不安全
法兰克 我真不喜欢克里姆林宫
Frank, I don't like the Kremlin so much.
不过我喜欢在底下
And I like being underneath it even less.
到了
Here we are.
太好了 没什么变化
That's great. It's just like yesterday.
这是我的旧铁撬 你们看
There's my crow bar. Look at this.
这里
There.
大家来看
Hey, look, chaps.
我的旧烟斗 我记得放在...
That's my old pipe. I knew I'd left it somewhere.
我妻子1969年给我的结婚礼物
My dear wife bought this for me in 1969. It was our wedding anniversay.
喔 对了
Oh yes!
这个是"暗影行动"
This is Nightshade, by the way.
这里
There.
那是什么
Is that...?
红色水银柱
That's Red Mercuy.
Red Mercuy?
我们冷战就是为了这个在拼命
We were always told it was a Cold War myth.
是 他们说制造不出来 但我做到了
Yes, they said it couldn't be done, but I did it.
如果这是真的红色水银柱
If that's Red Mercuy...
我们就可以用背包带着走
you can zip it up in a backpack and take it on the White House tour.
然后在不被发现的状况毁掉白宫
It's undetectable.
没有幅射 没有预兆
No signature. No fallout.
这是种需要能量平衡的武器
This weapon will entirely change the balance of international power...
就像...
overnight. Just like that.
我们都会死的
We're all gonna die.
跪下
On your knees.
卡嘉
Katia.
任何政府都不该拥有这武器
No government should have this weapon.
你们不能 我们也不能
Not yours. And not mine.
我有命令
I have orders.
这不是命令的事 是有关对与错的事
This isn't about orders. This is about right and wrong.
别过来
Don't.
你真的到美国来看我吗
Did you really come to see me in the States?
是的
Yes.
我屋子外的花是什么颜色
What color were the flowers outside my house?
黄色
Yellow.
我注意到你一直背靠着墙
I notice you are still holding up the wall.
瓦斯外泄 工作人员很快就会来了
Gas Leak, maintenance is coming
我叫帕夏
I am Pasha.
晚点去喝一杯吧
You want to get a drink later?
什么
Yes?
我想你也注意到我了
I thought perhaps you noticed me too!
这是在干什么
What in the name of? Hey!
你为什么吻这个家伙
What are you doing kissing this guy?
我不想杀他啊
I didn't wanna kill him.
这是什么狗屁逻辑
What kinda stupid logic is that?
她在这里做什么
What in the Sam Hill is she doing here?
她跟我们一起工作
She's working with us again.
就她吗
Like heck she is.
为什么吻那个家伙
Why were you kissing that guy?
孩子 不管发生什么事 你们都要留在克里姆林宫里
Kids, what happens in the Kremlin stays in the Kremlin.
你要对我解释一下
You are gonna have to explain this to me.
干杯
Hey, Comrades!
为我们的成功
Here's to more success.
成功
Success.
拯救世界
And saving the world!
拯救全世界
Saving the world!
我要接个电话 等一下回来
I got this. Right back.
嘿
Hey.
你在哪里
Where are you?
莫斯科
Moscow.
他不是疯子 法兰克
He's a nutter, Francis.
MI6关他不是因为他制造武器
MI6 didn't lock him up because he created the weapon...
因为他想要造反
but because he wants to see it go off.
哈罗 法兰克
Hello, Frank.
是维多利亚 对吗
That was Victoria, wasn't it?
说我是怪物之类的
Telling you that I was some sort of a monster...
想要摧毁苏维埃帝国
who once wanted to destroy the Soviet empire.
是 慢慢地
Yeah. Vey slowly.
这就对了
That's it. Good boy.
走前面
Good. In you go.
马文
Marvin...
放下武器
Guns down.
放下武器 慢慢转身
Weapons down. Vey slowly.
你一开始就在计划了 是吧
You planted the thing on WikiLeaks.
对 这是从警卫那里弄来的电话
Yes, it was a cell phone taken from a guard.
我恨不得就在MI6里面报仇
I was just itching to get my revenge on MI6.
法兰克 你能找到"青蛙" 只能说你运气好
Frank, you were absolutely marvelous the way you found The Frog.
别人都找不到
No one else could have found him.
杰克
Jack?
抱歉 法兰克 看来我要启动炸弹了
sorry, Frank, I made a deal already with Mr. Gordon for Red Mercuy.
做得好 贝利
Well done, Bailey.
谢谢
Thanks.
很高兴又见面了
Nice to see you again.
把枪收起来
Pick up the guns.
你的国家感谢你的牺牲
Your county appreciates your sacrifice.
你的时辰到了
But your time's up.
我们走
Let's go.
是时候了 贝利
It's time, Bailey.
对 是时候了
Yes, it is time.
很有趣 两名美国特工变成恐怖份子
Vey Interesting. Rogue American agents turned nuclear terrorists...
还杀了俄国官员
kill top Russian officer.
这可不太好
Not good.
再见 法兰克 再见 马文
So long, Frank. So long, Marvin.
来 跟我来
Come on, boys, let's go.
放松
Easy.
让我来开门
Please, let me take that from you.
我以为会在伦敦听到任务报告
I thought we were doing the debriefing in London.
是的
We were.
但你目前还不安全 我们要去科罗拉多
But since you're such a sick, twisted bastard, you're going to Colorado.
那里有个秘密基地 大约离地一英里
There's a secret facility there, about a mile underground...
你将留在那里渡过你的余生
where you will spend your remaining years...
包括你头脑里的一切知识
having evey bit of knowledge plucked from that giant head of yours.
真的吗
Really?
有趣的是 接下来的32年
Frankly, it will make your last 32 years...
就好像在加勒比海渡假一样
seem like a vacation in the Caribbean.
把他铐起来
Cuff him.
知道了
I say.
好吧 好吧
Well, well.
我打赌你一定没想到 是吗 老头？
Bet you didn't see that coming. Did you, old man?
我只能说我的确没有想到 很好
I must say, I didn't. Jolly good.
你先请
After you.
先生们 谢谢 早安
Thank you.Good morning, gentlemen.
他说什么
What did he say?
预备
Ready.
想想办法 想想办法
Do something. Do something.
我爱你
I love you.
至少韩不会先杀死我们
At least Han didn't get us first.
真的吗 你现在才说这些
Really? You're gonna bring that up right now?
世界上没有比这更性感的了
There is nothing more sey in the whole world...
一个漂亮的女人
than a beautiful woman...
跟一件绝妙的武器
with an incredible gun.
你在故做浪漫
You're such a romantic.
小心眼睛
Watch your eyes.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
我喜欢看你开枪时脚趾头的动作
I love the way your toes curl right before you fire.
真是没救了
Hopeless.
别动
Freeze.
我想你不该用那愚蠢的东西对着我
I don't think you ought to point that idiotic thing at me.
你应该好好想想自己的安全
You should really start thinking about your security protocol.
这是什么
What the hell is that?
这我的最爱
That my dear boy,
这是我制造过最强的神经毒剂 看吧
is an antidote...to the most powerul nerve agent ever created. Look.
永别了 年轻人
Hello, boys.
永别了 戴维先生
Hello, Mr. Davis.
你没想到会这样 对吗 老兄
And you didn't see that coming. Did you, old sport?
接下来的好戏你一定不愿意错过的
I'm sure you wouldn't want to miss what's coming ne.
这是一个小小的解药 很好
It's a little antidote. Jolly good.
很好
That's right.
好 谢谢
Good. Thank you.
很好
Jolly good.
说实话 法兰克 你才来这里两天而已
Honestly, Frank, 2 days and you're in front of a firing squad?
是的 但是
Yeah. But look...
别找藉口 你应该做更好的 真失望
No excuses. You're better than this. It's pathetic.
美国领导人飞去伦敦了
An American militay transport made an emergency landing in London.
飞机上所有的人都死了
Eveyone aboard was found dead.
贝利劫持伊朗大使馆人员当人质
Bailey has taken refuge in the Iranian embassy.
伊朗大使馆
The Iranian embassy?
我们必须去那里
We've gotta go there.
好 做好准备
All right. Get ready.
我看看能不能起飞
I'm gonna make sure we're cleared for takeoff.
如果世界没有毁灭的话
If the world is here in a week...
我会在土耳其的凯科斯群岛见你
I will meet you in the Turks and Caicos.
我们会在那里渡过每一个夜晚
And we will spend all night...
在星空下
beneath the stars.
我不会说韩语
I don't speak Korean!
你玩够了吗
You having fun yet?
告诉你 我玩得正高兴呢
I'll let you know when I start having fun.
你背叛了我
You betrayed me.
我身不由己
I had no choice.
如果是你也会这样做的
You'd have done the same thing, if you were me.
美国给了你多少钱
How much is the US paying you?
二千万
20 million.
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
我还想更多呢
I asked for more.
你怎么回事了
What happened to you?
以前你是很优秀的特工
You used to be a good agent.
停下 等等
Stop! Wait a minute.
听着 我需要你的帮助
Listen, I need your help.
我知道你想做正义之事
I know there's a part of you that wants to do the right thing.
有颗炸弹就要爆炸...
There is a weapon that's gonna be detonated...
胡说八道
Bullshit.
我没有胡说
It's not bullshit.
一颗炸弹就要降落到伦敦
There's a bomb headed for London right now.
如果不帮我 一千一百万人就会丧命
11 million people are gonna lose their lives if you don't help me.
好吧
All right.
我们走
Let's go.
这不表示以后我不会杀你
This doesn't mean I'm not going to kill you later.
我知道
I know.
我认为让你们维持关系的长久方法
I think the way to make a relationship work...
你们都不能放弃真正的自己
is that neither of you give up who you are.
你同意吗 马文
Don't you agree, Marvin?
就是这样 就像马文所说的
Exactly. Exactly what Marvin says.
爱情就像蹦极一样
Falling in love is like jumping off a cliff.
你必须相信他 并由他去
You just have to believe and let go.
天啊
My God!
还好吗
Are you okay?
不要 他没问题
No, he's All right.
他加入我们了
He's with us.
我们谈好了
We talked it out.
杀死贝利 解除武器 这很困难吗
Kill Bailey. Secure the weapon. How hard can it be?
当然外面有重兵把守 但是
The exernal security is vey heary but...
里面还有精英革命军
inside there are hardcore Revolutionary Guards.
他们都很狂热
They are serious fanatics.
整件事就靠她了
The whole thing depends on her.
你要明白 如果被捉到就死定了
You do realize, if they catch you, they will kill you.
伦敦
LONDON
我知道对你来说不容易 但是别担心
I know this won't be easy for you, but don't wory.
好吗
Okay?
我一直在想...
I've been thinking about...
你和我
you and me.
还有 我...
And I just...
我有东西给你
I got you something.
哇
Wow.
喜欢吗
You like it?
我很喜欢
I love it.
弹夹7发
7 rounds.
好
Okay.
我还没准备好
Not yet. I'm not ready.
停住 不
Stop, no.
不是现在 再等一下
Not right now. Wait.
如果错过 你会毁了一切的
If you don't do it, you're gonna blow it. Look at me.
我用英语数到三
I'm gonna count to 3. In English.
不是现在  等等
Not now. No. Wait.
2...
天啊
God damn it.
嗨
Hi.
她会被杀的
She's gonna get killed.
他们离开巢穴时很难有机会
It's tough when they leave the nest.
法兰克 拜托 相信我
Frank, come on. A little trust.
她拥有你我都没有的天赋
She has talents you and I will never have.
什么天赋
What talents?
人们都喜欢她
People like her.
如果她活下来 对你们的关系很有帮助
If she lives, this'll be good for your relationship.
你是对的
You're right.
我所知道的 女人与特工
And if there's one thing I know, it's women and covert ops.
这是两件事
That's 2 things.
不 小蚱蜢
No, grasshopper.
这不是
It is not.
我要告诉你一个秘密 部长先生
I wanna tell you a secret, Mr. Minister.
她也要和那家伙亲热了吗
Is she gonna make out with this guy, too?
这是什么玩意
What the hell was that?
毒药
Blomish poison.
你全身会感到麻痹和刺痛
Paralysis and shooting pains will grip your entire body.
你会慢慢窒息死亡
And you will slowly asph_iate until you choke to death...
除非你按照我所说的做
while remaining fully conscious, unless you do exactly what I say.
我会在损害国家名誉之前死去
I will die before I compromise my county.
我们会到你的办公室去
We will drive you to your office...
你要写一份官方文件
where you will write a letter on official stationey...
公开谴责在伊朗的女性医疗待遇
denouncing the treatment of women in Iran.
然后就会给你解药
Then you will get your antidote.
就这些
That's it?
伊朗大使馆 伦敦
IRANIAN EMBASSY, LONDON
我能帮你吗
How may I help you?
我想到伊朗避难
I would like to defect to Iran.
贝利教授 我为事情的延误道歉
Dr. Bailey, my apologies for the delay.
邓布拉斯教授已经检测了武器
Professor Dombrovski has declared the weapon authentic.
我们随时可以发射了
And we're prepared to proceed.
等我拿到我的钱 大使先生
As soon as my money's transferred, Mr. Ambassador.
滚开 我们的人
Move! She's with me.
阿曼
Arman?
他得离开这里
He needs to go.
好 好
Okay, okay.
你在说什么 她是谁
What are you talking about? Who is she?
先生 抱歉 你得离开了
Sir, I'm sorry, you need to leave.
你给我闭嘴
You need to shut up!
不
No.
这里怎么回事
What is happening here?
你在做什么
What are you doing?
告诉我怎么回事 她是谁
Tell me what is happening here! Who is she?
当我说滚出去 你就该滚出去
Get out! When I say "get out", get out of here!
你得走了
You need to go!
你妈的闭嘴
You shut the fuck up!
保险柜在那里
Where's the safe?
什么
What?
保险柜在那里
Where's the safe?
便便就要爆发了
Poo poo is coming.
24小时服务
24 Hour Plumbing.
快点 水管破了 快来
Hury. Emergency.Water everywhere. Come quick.
站住 等等
Stop! Plumbers, wait!
没事的 这边
It's okay! This way.
钱收到了
Money received.
干得好
Good show.
来看看我们的朋友
Let's see our friend here.
你能借我刀子吗
Would you lend me your knife, please?
谢谢
Thank you.
抱歉弄脏了地毯
sorry about the mess on the carpet.
哦 对了
Oh well.
从现在开始 杰克 我希望你不介意我叫你杰克吧
At this point, Jack... You don't mind me calling you "Jack", I hope.
你必须意识到
You must be beginning to comprehend...
自己的失败了
the stunning totality of your failure.
你不能给他们
You can't give it to them.
我没有兴趣给他们的
I've no more interest in giving Red Mercuy to these boys...
我会给你的
than I have in giving it to you.
天啊
Jesus.
在以前那个悲惨的世界 这只是我的想法
Yes, it's a sad old world. Anmay, that's only my opinion.
但是重点是这个
But the central point is this...
当时像你一样的MI6小杂种
when men like you and those dickheads from MI6...
那些CIA人员 或者其他为你做事的人
or CIA or whatever sewers you came from.
当你们不但毁了我的生活
When you take away not only my life...
夺去我心爱的妻子娜塔莎的无辜生命
but the innocent lives of my dear beloved wife Natasha...
及六岁的儿子
and my little boy, who was only 6.
我能说什么
What can I say?
你胆敢惹我 小子
When you mess with me, buddy...
你会付出代价的
this is what you get.
去你的 老家伙
Go to hell, old man.
再会了 爱国者
Fare thee well, patriot.
砰
Boom.
下一个是
Now what's ne?
华盛顿
Ah, Washington.
宝贝 嘿
Baby, hey.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
真厉害
Awesome!
天啊
Oh shit.
就这样
Is that it?
开始计时了 法兰克
It's counting down, Frank.
把它关了
Shut if off.
关掉 用什么关 气功
Shut Yeah. With what? Acupressure?
我怎么知道
I don't know.
为什么是我的责任
Why is it my responsibility?
做点什么
Just do something.
我的化学很烂
With my Mr. Chemisty set?
我不知道我在干什么
I don't know what I'm doing.
你要我按这个按钮吗
You want me to push a button?
贝利不见了 炸弹计时中
Bailey's loose and the bomb's ticking.
对不起 女士
Wait. Excuse me, ma'am.
你好 我有预约
Hello, I have an appointment.
有枪
Gun!
把炸弹拿远一点
Get that bomb outta here.
放下 亲爱的  对了
Drop it now, darling. That's right.
我的枪
My gun!
快按钮 下楼
Press the button. Ground floor.
马文 快点
Marvin, let's go!
很好玩
Jolly good show.
去你奶奶的
Bollocks.
你会开这荒唐的东西吗
You really drive this ridiculous thing?
你会射击吗
Can you shoot?
我需要指引 法兰克
We need eyes, Francis.
来吧 法兰克 剩40分钟
Come on, Frank. 40 minutes.
怎么样了
How ya doin' back there?
我现在不能说话
I can't talk to you right now.
如何呢
How is it?
非常好
It's fine.
操
Shit!
秀给我看看
Show me something.
维多利亚
Victoria...
我看见了 贝利正要去机场的路上
I got eyes on. Bailey's heading for the M4.
明白
Got it.
知道了
Got it!
这条剪了会停止或者爆炸
This one should stop it and this one should detonate it.
各50%的机率
It's fifty fifty.
等等
Wait!
不对劲
That's weird.
你知道自己在做什么吗
Do you have any idea what you're doing?
等等
Wait, wait!
停止剪那些电线
Stop cutting wires!
我知道我们都要死了
I knew we were gonna die!
准备好杀掉这贱人了吗
Ready to kill this son of a bitch?
随时准备着
Abso bloody lutely.
妈的
Damn it!
麻烦了
Trouble.
马文
Marvin!
需要两脚采踏板 两手握控制器
It's 2 pedals and 2 sticks.
好的
Okay.
见鬼 追丢了 他朝机场去了
Damn it! We missed him. He's going into the airport.
抓住他
Go get him!
你在哪里
Where are you?
有些麻烦事
In trouble.
飞回去 你在禁飞区中
Turn back! You are in restricted airspace.
我们马上要在空中爆炸了
They're gonna blow us outta the sky.
我一点也不担心
I wouldn't wory about that.
把引擎关掉
The engine's shutting down.
求救 求救
Mayday! Mayday!
法兰克!
Frank!
我知道我们要死了
I knew we were gonna die!
这是最后的警告
This is your last warning!
拜托告诉我 你们不是带了 大规模杀伤力武器坠落
Please, tell me you're not crashing with a weapon of mass destruction.
不 法兰克 不要啊
No, Frank, no.
天啊
Oh God.
你还好吗
You okay back there?
如果正确着陆多好 法兰克
It wasn't exactly a three point landing, Frank.
炸弹怎么样了
How's the bomb doing?
我无法停止它
I can't stop it.
我们要离开这里
We gotta get it outta here.
嘿
Hey!
下车
Get outta the car.
你好 法兰克
Hello, Frank.
欢迎登机
Welcome aboard.
你一直是个好士兵 不是吗
Always the good soldier, aren't you?
僵持状态
Stalemate.
你要如何救他出去
How will you take him out...
而不会打到她
and not shoot her first?
法兰克 没事的
Frank, it's okay.
你可以开枪 没事的
You can shoot. It's okay.
放下枪
Put the gun down.
Put the gun down!
把枪扔一边
Drop the gun!
放下枪 法兰克
Put the gun down, Frankie.
谢谢配合
Thank you.
很聪明
Pretty smart.
爱能征服一切啊
So love does conquer all.
你到那边去
Go to your golden warrior.
好女孩
That's a good girl.
过来
Come here.
真感人啊
It's so sweet.
现在离开飞机 带着那个炸弹
Now leave the plane. Take Nightshade with you.
再见了 法兰克
Bye, Frank.
做个好梦
Sweet dreams.
你为什么不开枪
Why didn't you just shoot me?
怎么了
What happened?
我不能停止倒数
I couldn't disarm it.
喔 见鬼
Crap.
马文
Marvin...
快要爆炸了吗
it's going to detonate?
是的
Yeah.
抱着我
Put your arms around me.
啊
Oh...
我怎么没预料到这个
I didn't see that one coming.
这种事不是每天都看得到喔
There's something you don't see evey day.
你把炸弹放到飞机上了
You put the bomb on the plane.
而你提都不提一下
And you didn't think to mention that?
你炸毁了我的飞机
You blew up my plane.
抱歉
sorry.
我错了 所以我们死期还未到嘛
I was wrong? So we're not even gonna die?
还没到
Not yet.
我甚至开始喜欢你了
I was actually starting to like you.
我也许不想杀你了
I was even thinking about not killing you.
就在你试着拯救全世界时
This is what happens when you Ty to save the world.
你不能计较这些
You can't put a price on these things.
你欠我 三千万的飞机 和 让我不杀你的二千万
You owe me 30 mil for the plane. And 20 for not killing you.
你已经死了 摩西
You're a dead man, Moses.
谢谢你的帮助
Thanks for your help.
真的
Really.
你认为他是认真的
You think he means it?
不 他是个好家伙
Nah, he's a nice guy.
我说真的 法兰克
I mean it, Frank!
好吧
All right.
他们做得对
They're going to be right as rain.
他寻求他的精神慰藉
He made the run to emotional safety.
所以
So...
我听说在加拉加斯有份工作
I did hear about this job in Caracas.
然后呢
And?
不要看我 她是你的女朋友
Don't look at me. She's your girlfriend.
走吧
Come on.